Guide to the Ira Vaughan Hiscock Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- OFFICE FILES, 1925-1939; Series II; 32.5 linear feet (78 boxes)
  - 1931 General Papers
    - Los Angeles, County of, Department of Health (Box 21, Folder 463-464)
      - Restricted (2 folders), 1931 January-August (Box 87)
    - Los Angeles, County of, Department of Health (Box 22, Folder 465)
    - M (Box 22, Folder 466-467)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund (Box 22, Folder 468)
    - Minneapolis, City of (Box 22, Folder 469)
    - N (Box 22, Folder 470)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, Inc. (Box 22, Folder 471-474)
    - National Tuberculosis Association (Box 22, Folder 475)
    - New England Health Institute (Box 22, Folder 476)
    - New Haven, A-Z (Box 22, Folder 477)
    - New Haven Cancer Control Committee (Box 23, Folder 478-479)
    - New Haven Chamber of Commerce (Box 23, Folder 480)
    - New Haven, City of (Box 23, Folder 481)
    - New Haven, City of, Department of Health (Box 23, Folder 482-484)
    - New Haven Community Chest (Box 23, Folder 485-489)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies (Box 24, Folder 490-491)
    - New Haven, Family Society of (Box 24, Folder 492)
    - New Haven Hospital (Box 24, Folder 493)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse Association (Box 24, Folder 494-495)
    - New York City, A-Z (Box 24, Folder 496)
    - New York, City of (Box 24, Folder 497)
    - New York, City of, Committee on Neighborhood Health Development (Box 24, Folder 498)
    - New York, State of (Box 24, Folder 499)
    - O (Box 24, Folder 500)
    - Ohio Public Health Association (Box 24, Folder 501)
    - Ohio, State of (Box 24, Folder 502)
    - P (Box 24, Folder 503)
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 24, Folder 504)
    - Public Health Federation (Box 24, Folder 505)
    - Q (Box 24, Folder 506)
    - R (Box 24, Folder 507)
    - Racine, Wisconsin (Box 24, Folder 508)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 24, Folder 509)
    - Russell Sage Foundation (Box 24, Folder 510)
    - S (Box 24, Folder 511)
    - San Francisco, California (Box 24, Folder 512)
    - Syracuse, New York (Box 24, Folder 513)
    - T (Box 24, Folder 514)
    - U (Box 24, Folder 515)
    - United States Department of Agriculture (Box 24, Folder 516)
    - United States Department of Labor (Box 24, Folder 516)
    - United States Treasury Department, Public Health Service (Box 24, Folder 517)
    - W (Box 24, Folder 518)
    - Wesleyan University (Box 24, Folder 519)
    - White House Conference on Child Health and Protection (Box 25, Folder 520)
    - Winslow, C.-E.A. (Box 25, Folder 521)
    - Y (Box 25, Folder 522)
    - Yale University, A-Z (Box 25, Folder 523-524)
      - Restricted, 1931 (Box 87)
        Materials are restricted until January 1, 2032.
    - Yale University Graduate School (Box 25, Folder 525)
    - Yale University, School of Medicine (Box 25, Folder 526-531)
      - Restricted (3 folders), 1931 (Box 87)
  - 1931 Surveys
    - Health Center Study (Box 25, Folder 532-533)
    - Health Center Study (Box 26, Folder 534)
    - Public health surveys (Box 26, Folder 535)
    - School Absenteeism Study (Box 26, Folder 536)
  - 1931 Writings (Box 26, Folder 537-540)
  - 1932 General Papers
    - A (Box 27, Folder 541)
    - American Child Health Association (Box 27, Folder 542)
    - American Epidemiological Society (Box 27, Folder 543)
    - American Medical Association (Box 27, Folder 544)
    - American Public Health Association (Box 27, Folder 545-559)
    - American Public Health Association (Box 28, Folder 560-562)
    - American Social Hygiene Association (Box 28, Folder 563)
    - B (Box 28, Folder 564)
    - Bellevue-Yorkville Health Demonstration (Box 28, Folder 565)
    - Boy Scouts of America, New Haven Council (Box 28, Folder 566-568)
    - C (Box 28, Folder 569)
    - California, State of, Department of Public Health (Box 28, Folder 570)
    - Committee on the Costs of Medical Care (Box 28, Folder 571-573)
    - Commonwealth Fund (Box 28, Folder 574-577)
    - Commonwealth Fund (Box 29, Folder 578)
    - Connecticut, A-Z (Box 29, Folder 579)
    - Connecticut Conference of Social Work (Box 29, Folder 580)
    - Connecticut Dairy and Food Council (Box 29, Folder 581)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association (Box 29, Folder 582)
    - Connecticut Society for Mental Hygiene, New Haven branch (Box 29, Folder 583-584)
    - Connecticut, State of, Board of Education (Box 29, Folder 585)
    - Connecticut, State of, Bureau of Adult Welfare (Box 29, Folder 585)
    - Connecticut, State of, Department of Health (Box 29, Folder 586)
    - Detroit, City of, Department of Health (Box 29, Folder 587)
    - Delta Omega Society (Box 29, Folder 588-589)
    - E (Box 29, Folder 590)
    - F (Box 29, Folder 591)
    - G (Box 29, Folder 592)
    - Greenwich, Connecticut (Box 29, Folder 593)
    - H (Box 29, Folder 594)
    - Hancock (John) Mutual Life Insurance Company (Box 29, Folder 595)
    - Honolulu, Hawaii (Box 29, Folder 596)
    - I (Box 29, Folder 597)
    - International Association of Dairy and Milk Inspectors (Box 29, Folder 598-599)
    - J (Box 29, Folder 600)
    - K (Box 29, Folder 601)
    - L (Box 29, Folder 602)
    - Los Angeles, County of, Department of Health (Box 29, Folder 603)
    - Los Angeles, County of, Department of Health (Box 30, Folder 604)
    - M (Box 30, Folder 605)
    - Massachusetts, State of, Department of Public Health (Box 30, Folder 606)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund (Box 30, Folder 607-610)
    - N (Box 30, Folder 611)
    - National Committee of Health Council Executives (Box 30, Folder 612)
    - National Conference of Social Work (Box 30, Folder 613)
    - National Dairy Council (Box 30, Folder 614)
    - National Organization of Public Health Nursing, Inc. (Box 30, Folder 615)
    - National Social Work Council (Box 30, Folder 616)
    - National Tuberculosis Association (Box 30, Folder 617)
    - New Haven, A-Z (Box 30, Folder 618)
    - New Haven Cancer Control Committee (Box 30, Folder 619-621)
    - New Haven Cancer Control Committee (Box 31, Folder 622-623)
    - New Haven Chamber of Commerce (Box 31, Folder 624)
    - New Haven, City of, Department of Health (Box 31, Folder 625-629)
      - Restricted, 1932 (Box 87)
    - New Haven Committee on a Community Health Project (Box 31, Folder 630)
    - New Haven Committee on Unemployment Relief (Box 31, Folder 631)
    - New Haven Community Chest (Box 31, Folder 632-638)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies (Box 31, Folder 639-642)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies (Box 32, Folder 643-645)
    - New Haven County Public Health Association (Box 32, Folder 646)
    - New Haven, Family Society of (Box 32, Folder 647)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse Association (Box 32, Folder 648)
    - New York City, A-Z (Box 32, Folder 649)
    - New York, State of, Department of Health (Box 32, Folder 650)
    - P (Box 32, Folder 651)
    - Q (Box 32, Folder 652)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 32, Folder 653)
    - Russell Sage Foundation (Box 32, Folder 654)
    - S (Box 32, Folder 655)
    - Stratford Community Health Project (Box 32, Folder 656-657)
    - T (Box 32, Folder 658)
    - United States Department of Commerce (Box 32, Folder 659)
    - United States Department of Labor (Box 32, Folder 660)
    - United States Treasury Department, Public Health Service (Box 32, Folder 661)
    - W (Box 32, Folder 662)
    - Wesleyan University (Box 32, Folder 663)
    - White House Conference on Child Health and Protection (Box 32, Folder 664)
    - Winslow, C.-E. A. (Box 32, Folder 665)
    - Y (Box 32, Folder 666)
    - Yale University, A-Z (Box 32, Folder 667-671)
    - Yale University Graduate School (Box 32, Folder 672)
    - Yale University, School of Medicine (Box 33, Folder 673-678)
    - Yale University, Sigma Xi Society (Box 33, Folder 679)
  - 1932 Surveys
    - Public health surveys (Box 33, Folder 680)
  - 1932 Writings (Box 33, Folder 681-685)
  - 1933 General Papers
    - A (Box 34, Folder 686)
    - American Child Health Association (Box 34, Folder 687)
    - American Epidemiological Society (Box 34, Folder 687)
    - American Public Health Association (Box 34, Folder 688-696)
    - American Social Hygiene Association (Box 34, Folder 697)
    - B (Box 34, Folder 698)
    - Bellevue-Yorkville Health Demonstration (Box 34, Folder 699)
    - Boy Scouts of America, New Haven Council (Box 35, Folder 700-701)
    - C (Box 35, Folder 702)
    - Cattaraugus County School Health Service (Box 35, Folder 703)
    - Commonwealth Fund (Box 35, Folder 704-705)
    - Connecticut, A-Z (Box 35, Folder 706)
    - Connecticut Dairy and Food Council (Box 35, Folder 707)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association (Box 35, Folder 708)
    - Connecticut Society for Mental Hygiene, New Haven branch (Box 35, Folder 709)
    - Connecticut, State of (Box 35, Folder 710)
    - Connecticut, State of, Department of Health (Box 35, Folder 711-712)
    - Delta Omega Society (Box 35, Folder 713)
    - E (Box 35, Folder 714)
    - Emerson, Haven (Box 35, Folder 715)
    - F-G (Box 35, Folder 716)
    - H (Box 35, Folder 717)
    - Hamden Hall School (Box 35, Folder 718)
    - Honolulu, Hawaii (Box 35, Folder 719)
    - International Association of Dairy and Milk Inspectors (Box 35, Folder 720)
    - J-K (Box 36, Folder 721)
    - L (Box 36, Folder 722)
    - Los Angeles, County of (Box 36, Folder 723)
    - M (Box 36, Folder 724)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 36, Folder 725)
    - Massachusetts, State of, Department of Health (Box 36, Folder 726)
    - Massachusetts Tuberculosis League, Inc. (Box 36, Folder 727)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund (Box 36, Folder 728)
    - N (Box 36, Folder 729)
    - National Conference of Social Work (Box 36, Folder 730)
    - National Dairy Council (Box 36, Folder 731)
    - National Health Council, Inc. (Box 36, Folder 732)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, Inc. (Box 36, Folder 733)
    - National Tuberculosis Association (Box 36, Folder 734)
    - New Haven, A-Z (Box 36, Folder 735)
    - New Haven Cancer Control Committee (Box 36, Folder 736)
    - New Haven Chamber of Commerce (Box 36, Folder 737-738)
    - New Haven, City of, Department of Health (Box 36, Folder 739-741)
    - New Haven Community Chest (Box 37, Folder 742-745)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies (Box 37, Folder 746-754)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies (Box 38, Folder 755)
    - New Haven, Family Society of (Box 38, Folder 756-759)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse Association (Box 38, Folder 760)
    - New York, A-Z (Box 38, Folder 761)
    - New York, City of, Department of Health (Box 38, Folder 762)
    - New York, State of, Department of Health (Box 38, Folder 763)
    - O-R (Box 38, Folder 764)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 38, Folder 765)
    - Russell Sage Foundation (Box 38, Folder 766)
    - S (Box 38, Folder 767)
    - Stratford (Connecticut): Sterling Park (Box 38, Folder 768)
    - T (Box 38, Folder 769)
    - U-V (Box 38, Folder 770)
    - W (Box 38, Folder 771)
    - Winslow, C.-E. A. (Box 38, Folder 772)
    - Y (Box 38, Folder 773)
    - Yale University, A-Z (Box 38, Folder 774-775)
      - Restricted, 1933 (Box 87)
    - Yale University, A-Z (Box 39, Folder 776-779)
      - Restricted, 1933 April-June (Box 87)
    - Yale University Graduate School (Box 39, Folder 780)
    - Yale University, School of Medicine (Box 39, Folder 781-783)
      - Restricted, 1933 (Box 87)
  - 1933 Surveys
    - Public health surveys (Box 39, Folder 784)
  - 1933 Writings (Box 39, Folder 785-787)
  - 1933 Writings (Box 40, Folder 788-790)
  - 1934 General Papers
    - A (Box 40, Folder 791)
    - American Child Health Association (Box 40, Folder 792)
    - American Epidemiological Society (Box 40, Folder 793)
    - American Medical Association (Box 40, Folder 794)
    - American Public Health Association (Box 40, Folder 795-804)
    - American Social Hygiene Association (Box 41, Folder 805)
    - B (Box 41, Folder 806)
    - Blydenburgh, George T. (Box 41, Folder 807)
    - Boy Scouts of America, National Council (Box 41, Folder 808-809)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Southern New Haven County Council (Box 41, Folder 810)
    - Bunnell, Rebecca (Mrs. Sterling H.) (Box 41, Folder 811)
    - C (Box 41, Folder 812)
    - California, State of (Box 41, Folder 813)
    - Commonwealth Fund (Box 41, Folder 814-817)
    - Connecticut, A-Z (Box 41, Folder 818)
    - Connecticut Dairy and Food Council (Box 41, Folder 819)
    - Connecticut Society for Mental Hygiene, New Haven branch (Box 41, Folder 820)
    - Connecticut, State of (Box 41, Folder 821)
    - Connecticut, State of, Department of Health (Box 41, Folder 822)
    - D (Box 41, Folder 823)
    - Delta Omega Society (Box 41, Folder 824)
    - E (Box 41, Folder 825)
    - F (Box 41, Folder 826)
    - Falk, Isidore S. (Box 41, Folder 827)
    - Federal Emergency Relief Administration (Box 41, Folder 828)
    - G (Box 41, Folder 829)
    - H (Box 41, Folder 830)
    - Hartford, Connecticut (Box 41, Folder 831)
    - Honolulu, Hawaii (Box 41, Folder 832)
    - International Association of Dairy and Milk Inspectors (Box 42, Folder 833-834)
    - L (Box 42, Folder 835)
    - Los Angeles, County of, Department of Health (Box 42, Folder 836)
    - M (Box 42, Folder 837)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company (Box 42, Folder 838)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund (Box 42, Folder 839-840)
    - N (Box 42, Folder 841)
    - National Committee of Health Council Executives (Box 42, Folder 842)
    - National Conference of Social Work (Box 42, Folder 843)
    - National Health Council, Inc. (Box 42, Folder 844)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, Inc. (Box 42, Folder 845)
    - National Tuberculosis Association (Box 42, Folder 846)
    - New Haven, A-Z (Box 42, Folder 847)
    - New Haven Cancer Control Committee (Box 42, Folder 848)
    - New Haven Chamber of Commerce (Box 42, Folder 849-850)
    - New Haven, City of, Department of Health (Box 42, Folder 851-854)
    - New Haven, City of, Department of Health (Box 43, Folder 855-860)
    - New Haven Community Chest (Box 43, Folder 861-868)
    - New Haven Community Chest (Box 44, Folder 869-871)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies (Box 44, Folder 872-880)
    - New Haven County Public Health Association (Box 44, Folder 881)
    - New Haven, Family Society of (Box 44, Folder 882-883)
    - New Haven Rotary Club (Box 44, Folder 884-886)
    - New Haven Rotary Club (Box 45, Folder 887)
    - New Haven Taxpayers, Inc. (Box 45, Folder 888)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse Association (Box 45, Folder 888)
    - New York, City of, Department of Health (Box 45, Folder 889-892)
    - New York Social Work Publicity Council (Box 45, Folder 893)
    - New York, State of (Box 45, Folder 894)
    - P (Box 45, Folder 895)
    - Pasadena, City of, Health Department (Box 45, Folder 896)
    - Philadelphia Inter-State Dairy Council (Box 45, Folder 897)
    - Q (Box 45, Folder 898)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 45, Folder 899)
    - Russell Sage Foundation (Box 45, Folder 900)
    - S (Box 45, Folder 901)
    - T (Box 45, Folder 902)
    - United States, A-Z (Box 45, Folder 903)
    - United States Department of Labor (Box 45, Folder 904)
    - V-W (Box 45, Folder 905)
    - Wesleyan University (Box 45, Folder 906)
    - Winslow, C.-E. A. (Box 45, Folder 907)
    - Yale University, A-Z (Box 45, Folder 908-912)
      - Restricted, 1934 (Box 87)
    - Yale University, School of Medicine (Box 45, Folder 913-915)
    - Yale University, School of Medicine (Box 46, Folder 916-919)
  - 1934 Surveys
    - Hartford survey (Box 46, Folder 920)
    - Public health surveys (Box 46, Folder 921)
  - 1934 Writings (Box 46, Folder 922-925)
  - 1934 Writings (Box 47, Folder 926-928)
  - 1935 General Papers
    - A (Box 47, Folder 929)
    - American Child Health Association (Box 47, Folder 930)
    - American Medical Association (Box 47, Folder 930)
    - American Public Health Association (Box 47, Folder 931-935)
    - American Social Hygiene Association (Box 47, Folder 936)
    - B (Box 47, Folder 937)
    - Baltimore, City of, Department of Health (Box 47, Folder 938)
    - Boy Scouts of America, National Council (Box 47, Folder 939)
    - Boy Scouts of America, National Council (Box 48, Folder 940)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Quinnipiac Council, New Haven (Box 48, Folder 941)
    - Bundesen, Herman N. (Box 48, Folder 942)
    - Bunnell, Sterling H. (Box 48, Folder 942)
    - C (Box 48, Folder 943)
    - California, State of, Department of Public Health (Box 48, Folder 944)
    - Calver, Homer N. (Box 48, Folder 944)
    - Cattaraugus County School Health Service (Box 48, Folder 945)
    - Cleveland Health Council (Box 48, Folder 946)
    - Committee on Economic Security (Box 48, Folder 946)
    - Commonwealth Fund (Box 48, Folder 947-948)
    - Community Chests and Councils, Inc. (Box 48, Folder 949)
    - Connecticut, A-Z (Box 48, Folder 950)
    - Connecticut Society for Mental Hygiene, New Haven branch (Box 48, Folder 951)
    - Connecticut, State of (Box 48, Folder 952)
    - Connecticut, State of, Department of Health (Box 48, Folder 953)
    - D (Box 48, Folder 954)
    - F- G (Box 48, Folder 955)
    - H (Box 48, Folder 956)
    - Hamden Hall School (Box 48, Folder 957)
    - I (Box 48, Folder 958)
    - International Association of Dairy and Milk Inspectors (Box 48, Folder 959)
    - J-K (Box 48, Folder 960)
    - L (Box 48, Folder 961)
    - Leathers, W. S. (Box 48, Folder 962)
    - Los Angeles, County of (Box 48, Folder 963)
    - M (Box 48, Folder 964)
    - Massachusetts, State of Metropolitan Life Insurance Company (Box 49, Folder 965)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund (Box 49, Folder 966-967)
    - N (Box 49, Folder 968)
    - National Conference of Social Work (Box 49, Folder 969)
    - National Health Council, Inc. (Box 49, Folder 970-973)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, Inc. (Box 49, Folder 974)
    - National Tuberculosis Association (Box 49, Folder 975-977)
    - New Haven, A-Z (Box 49, Folder 978)
    - New Haven Cancer Control Committee (Box 49, Folder 979)
    - New Haven Chamber of Commerce (Box 49, Folder 980)
    - New Haven, City of (Box 49, Folder 981)
    - New Haven, City of, Department of Health (Box 49, Folder 982)
    - New Haven, City of, Department of Health (Box 50, Folder 983-984)
    - New Haven Community Chest (Box 50, Folder 985-990)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies (Box 50, Folder 991-994)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies (Box 51, Folder 995)
    - New Haven County Public Health Association (Box 51, Folder 996)
    - New Haven Dental Clinic Society (Box 51, Folder 997)
    - New Haven, Family Society of (Box 51, Folder 998)
    - New Haven Rotary Club (Box 51, Folder 999-1001)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse Association (Box 51, Folder 1002-1003)
    - New York City, A-Z (Box 51, Folder 1004)
    - New York, City of (Box 51, Folder 1005)
    - New York, City of, Department of Health (Box 51, Folder 1006)
    - New York, State of (Box 51, Folder 1007)
    - O (Box 51, Folder 1008)
    - P-Q (Box 51, Folder 1009)
    - Pasadena, City of (Box 51, Folder 1010)
    - R (Box 52, Folder 1011)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 52, Folder 1012)
    - Russell Sage Foundation (Box 52, Folder 1013)
    - S (Box 52, Folder 1014)
    - Shepard, William P. (Box 52, Folder 1015)
    - T (Box 52, Folder 1016)
    - Tennessee, State of (Box 52, Folder 1017)
    - V (Box 52, Folder 1018)
    - Vaughan, Henry F. (Box 52, Folder 1019)
    - United States, A-Z (Box 52, Folder 1020)
    - United States Army (Box 52, Folder 1021-1022)
    - W (Box 52, Folder 1023)
    - Y (Box 52, Folder 1024)
    - Yale University, School of Medicine (Box 52, Folder 1025-1039)
      - Restricted, 1935 (Box 87)
    - Yale University, School of Medicine (Box 53, Folder 1040-1048)
  - 1935 Surveys
    - Honolulu survey (Box 53, Folder 1049-1054)
  - 1935 Writings (Box 54, Folder 1055-1061)
  - 1936 General Papers
    - A (Box 55, Folder 1062)
    - American Epidemiological Society (Box 55, Folder 1063)
    - American Medical Association (Box 55, Folder 1064)
    - American Public Health Association (Box 55, Folder 1065-1068)
    - American Social Hygiene Association (Box 55, Folder 1069)
    - B (Box 55, Folder 1070)
    - Baumgartner, Leona (Box 55, Folder 1071)
    - Blue Ridge Institute for Social Work Executives (Box 55, Folder 1072)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Quinnipiac Council, New Haven (Box 55, Folder 1073-1079)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Quinnipiac Council, New Haven (Box 56, Folder 1080)
    - Brainard, C. Brewster (Box 56, Folder 1081)
    - Brown, Philip King (Box 56, Folder 1082)
    - Bunnell, Sterling H. (Box 56, Folder 1082)
    - C (Box 56, Folder 1083)
    - California, A-Z (Box 56, Folder 1084)
    - California, State of (Box 56, Folder 1085)
    - California, University of (Box 56, Folder 1086)
    - California, University of Southern (Box 56, Folder 1087)
    - Calver, Homer N. (Box 56, Folder 1088)
    - Cattaraugus County School Health Service (Box 56, Folder 1089)
    - Cleveland Anti-Tuberculosis League (Box 56, Folder 1090)
    - Cleveland Health Council (Box 56, Folder 1091)
    - Commonwealth Fund (Box 56, Folder 1092-1093)
    - Community Chests and Councils, Inc. (Box 56, Folder 1094)
    - Connecticut, A-Z (Box 56, Folder 1095)
    - Connecticut Conference of Social Work (Box 56, Folder 1096)
    - Connecticut Society for Mental Hygiene, New Haven branch (Box 56, Folder 1097-1098)
    - Connecticut, State of (Box 56, Folder 1099)
    - Connecticut, State of, Department of Health (Box 56, Folder 1100)
    - D (Box 56, Folder 1101)
    - Detroit, City of, Department of Health (Box 57, Folder 1102)
    - E (Box 57, Folder 1103)
    - F (Box 57, Folder 1104)
    - Falk, Isidore S. (Box 57, Folder 1105)
    - Fitzgerald, J. G. (Box 57, Folder 1105)
    - Foote, Franklin M. (Box 57, Folder 1105)
    - G (Box 57, Folder 1106)
    - H. (Box 57, Folder 1107)
    - Halverson, Wilton L. (Box 57, Folder 1108)
    - Hartford, City of, Board of Education (Box 57, Folder 1109)
    - Hartford, City of, Board of Health Commissioners (Box 57, Folder 1109)
    - Hartford National Bank and Trust Company (Box 57, Folder 1109)
    - Hiscock, Ira V. (Box 57, Folder 1110)
    - Honolulu, Hawaii (Box 57, Folder 1111-1114)
    - Hospital Corporation of Southington, Connecticut (Box 57, Folder 1115)
    - I (Box 57, Folder 1116)
    - International Association of Dairy and Milk Inspectors (Box 57, Folder 1117)
    - International Association of Milk Sanitarians (Box 57, Folder 1118)
    - J-K (Box 57, Folder 1119)
    - L (Box 57, Folder 1120)
    - Los Angeles, County of, Department of Health (Box 57, Folder 1121)
    - M (Box 57, Folder 1122)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company (Box 57, Folder 1123)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund (Box 57, Folder 1124-1125)
    - N (Box 58, Folder 1126)
    - National Conference of Social Work (Box 58, Folder 1127)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, Inc. (Box 58, Folder 1128-1129)
    - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, Inc. (Box 58, Folder 1130)
    - National Tuberculosis Association (Box 58, Folder 1131-1132)
    - New Haven, A-Z (Box 58, Folder 1133)
    - New Haven Cancer Control Committee (Box 58, Folder 1134)
    - New Haven Chamber of Commerce (Box 58, Folder 1135)
    - New Haven, City of (Box 58, Folder 1136)
    - New Haven, City of, Department of Health (Box 58, Folder 1137-1139)
    - New Haven Community Chest (Box 58, Folder 1140-1142)
    - New Haven Community Chest (Box 59, Folder 1143-1148)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies (Box 59, Folder 1149-1152)
    - New Haven County Public Health Association (Box 59, Folder 1153)
    - New Haven, Family Society of (Box 59, Folder 1154)